It's an orange parfum
I'll never celebrate tonight
Let's make it fun!
With the co-dream concert of 道路市
There is reduced to five steps
there you go
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
In our previous episode, we found out
that you can equip boobs.
What exactly does equip mean?
They attach to the chest?
The Holy Grail.
Poop's Neo sister.
Oh.
Wow.
I see now.
Dang, those are major jumbo chunks.
Breast plates are an awesome tool when you're trying
recreate an extra pronounced chest it's super hard to get the same effect with your standard padding
true that i wore two new brawls trying to boob up for shizuku-tan i low-key strangled myself
i bet these are also great when a character has an exposed chest but you don't want to show skin
whoa like show off the fake girls and hide the real ones let me show you i apologize in advance
wakana for what these are size for women so it might be tight on you
what there you have it dude they're not even your boobs what are you embarrassed about
if you want to look around they sell way more cosplay gear than just boobs all of this is for
cosplay look at this stuff it's all new to me professional stage makeup is hard to find
because it's made for pros the coverage is good and the color turns out great in pics that's awesome
i love uh himeno i've been wondering about something and what's that your interest is cosplaying women
right of course it is could you please share your cross-playing tips and tricks
see i've helped girls cosplay guys before but i've never helped guys cosplay girls i would love to
hear about your methods anything would help uh lend us your cause wisdom wise one yeah i'd be happy to
teach you we can't thank you enough when guys cosplay girls focus on the eyes using a warm toned
eyeliner to deepen the crease under your eyes really makes them pop i find it makes mine bigger and more
youthful i so see it my eyes are drawn straight to them i don't have much of a shadow there so i'm always
sure to draw it on sparkly eyes are the key to cuteness it only takes a second to amp up your look
this is part of my daily makeup routine but looking at you now i'm totally messing something up
maybe a little all the makeup you're using for your current look is pink right yep had to be
subo-chan's signature color is pink and branding is everything to idols i'm the cutest idol in the
universe how thoughtful whoa even your eye shadow is pink huh it's totes adorbs thank you it's actually
just a drugstore brand you've got mad skills i thought of another tip for you huh buy this orange
concealer yep it's a must-have for me is it to hide dark circles i believe i read somewhere that orange
concealer is the best for that right but i have another use for it to hide my five o'clock shadow
oh yeah it's easy to forget you're a dude xy gang he does sound like a guy when he laughs
my facial hair isn't dark or anything but i never wanted to stand out
if you shave your brows it covers that stubble too we could use that to eat we must consume
how useful she shaves her eyebrows clean off that's pretty bold marine
one of my favorite things to do in my daily makeup routine is add glitter under my eyes this is so
fun exchanging information and learning new things it's the best i'm also a fan of using the same
shadow in my eyes and brows we still have so much left to try isn't this gnarly gojo i can't get over
all the different options if i put all the stuff they have here i could coordinate makeup to a green
wig or a red wig your passion is admirable yet hilarious hey gojo i'm gonna go check out the
contacts okay oh question what is that i'm pretty sure it's used for crafting like for building weapons
and stuff it's not exactly my expertise sculpting that's cool and these are character wigs
huh these seem a little bit more complicated than the standard wigs i buy at swallowtail
i forgot you style your own wigs so you haven't bought one of these before they sell different
pre-styled wigs for different characters and stuff like this you can clip it on and go it came off so
easily they sell costumes on the third floor this is actually where i got subaru's outfit the whole
costume i'm not the crafty type i can't style or make much so i shop instead i would be useless with
a sewing machine i'm super thankful specialty shops like this exist they let me get everything i need
a quick trip to the store and i can cosplay whatever and whenever i want
places like this are huge for people who can't build their own costumes or don't have the time
its existence validates cosplaying which is a really awesome thing so yeah i love it here
yeah okay here we go
this is exactly like in the game i love how subaru is a total ice queen during fan interactions
besties got eyes for her beloved manager and nobody else she looks like a cinnamon roll but could totally
kill you ice queen
oh oh hang on i can't fix it for you if you don't stand still right
excuse me is it cool if we get a picture together
you look perfect your subaru is seriously killer we would love to take some pics would you mind
you girls are sweet just know under the makeup i'm a guy
huh if you don't mind that then let's take some pics
huh
we stand you're a literal wizard
my brain is breaking you're so screen accurate i couldn't tell you were a guy like it
oh my gosh you're so pretty and confident you're about to move me to actual tears
get it girly same here if you'd like i could take the photos yes please everyone get ready
oh no i'm not in cosplay huh it's your base look cool yeah thanks this is epic it's like a slice
of life scene where the idols stop by the park on their way home from school and i love slice of life
scenes cosplay events are the greatest hey i'd like to take some pics too can i snap a few candidates
of course
thanks for an awesome day yes thank you guys
hanging out with other cosplayers just gives me so much life i got lots of love i think more people
noticed my cosplay this time subarune did just play second after all people noticed you because your
subarune is effing adorable well thank you so what was it that got you into cosplay in the first place
your love for best girl subarune
nah you're right i do love subarune but she's not why i started
the first time i ever put on makeup was in my second year of high school it was my big sister's
idea hey you'd be way prettier than the dudes on that show i have a wig and could slay your makeup
let's do it oh i watched that show too yeah it was pretty funny i have it to think from my first
experience with makeup
heck yeah you look beautiful when i saw myself in the mirror i was shocked by how radically different i
looked there was no moving past it after that naturally i had my sister teach me how to do makeup
she even gave me her old clothes she didn't wear anymore that's so nice sister of the year award
yep she's the best once i got more comfortable i decided to try cosplay with subarune character
makeup is a completely different piece so it took some time but it was incredibly worth it i had so
much fun my family is super open-minded my mom even gave me some of her makeup tips
she always compliments me when i get better it makes my day
i'm not very tall and my voice is pretty high i would get teased all the time it cuddled fast
i just can't see him as a guy yeah he's got weird vibes the wind could beat you up like dude eat
some burgers it made me hate myself but when i started cosplaying i could step into a character and
pretend to be them for a while and then i began to love myself maybe subaru chan's confidence rubbed off
on me
the more i cosplayed the more confident i became i stopped being such a nervous wreck around other people
when i got to college a girl asked me out for the very first time
you better invite me in wow cleaner than i thought it'd be
what is this that's when she found my outfits
what the hell you're living with another woman aren't you no all those clothes are actually mine
they're all yours do you think i'm dumb there's no guy alive that would want all this frilly crap
i'm not lying i i dress like a girl sometimes i guess you could call it my hobby
why would you pick a hobby like that just throw that stuff away it's insanely creepy
oh okay so i did what i had to
i dumped that chick on the spot
sorry to spill all my craziness on you guys out of the blue
we're sorry
don't be that was definitely tmi
are you okay not okay folks did i say something you're making this too adorable don't cry on my
behalf it's just i mean she saw how pretty your outfits were she should have been able to tell how
how much they meant to you how they made you feel how could she tell you to throw something you love in the garbage
that's cruel i can't just hear that and what it's like
i think you but i promised i've moved past it i'm fine now
see when my ex told me to give it up i tried to imagine living the rest of my life without cosplay
it scared me it's my passion i knew i'd blame my regrets on her and if i gave up the thing that
made me confident i would just hate myself even more so i didn't and i love myself more every day
all right there's really nothing to cry about okay need a tissue you're such a saint
you don't hold back huh to tell you the truth i do keep my guard up when you asked me about
cosplaying female characters i was nervous i thought you might tell me i'm creepy i would never
i swear it's your passion and you're amazing at it
well thank you sorry i doubted you honestly today was exactly the thing i needed everyone knew that i
was a guy and no one thought i was creepy at all just because one person was too small-minded
doesn't mean everyone i meet will be the same people are kind especially you two
gosh it's funny i came to the cosplay event today on a whim
but i'm glad i did thank you my coffee was delicious of course glad you liked it thank you for
making my day so special maybe we can even be buddies at the next event we're all at too
totes oh absolutely really yay well see ya
he's like a stupidly handsome boy he's 20 stupidly handsome man
those two are cute i hope they stick together
grandpa lunch is almost ready coming
all right you said you're going out this afternoon i am i'll let you know if it looks
like i'll be late sure i'll see you later see you then now go have fun
uh are you sure it was okay for me to tag along yes maureen let us know that you were coming so it's
really no trouble amateur models often bring their boyfriends so they can scurry off on dates while
their makeup is done guess that makes sense
you know that jacket seems heavy these outfits would be perfect for winter but it feels too early for
them because everything they've dressed her in is intended for winter fashion magazines do shoots
three or four months in advance that seems really early it would be fine if everyone wasn't melting from
the heat yeah that sounds rough help me before i didn't really know anything about all her modeling
work but she has been doing something amazing it's so cool maureen is an incredibly versatile model
she can pull off any makeup look and any outfit just a flick of her eyes and she's a whole new person
it's true she's different from how she is normally or when she's in cosplay
starting out we didn't really see very much of her but lately she's been showing up left and right
DSLRs are pricey and i gotta write that check
maureen is a fan favorite with many of our readers
she sort of feels like the it girl intimidating in a good way sometimes she even feels too cool for us
a perfectly mysterious model
kitagawa this world is so dazzling and i never even knew about it
all that said i've asked her to be an exclusive model for our magazine at least a dozen times but
she says she's too busy with her hobbies and won't get on board please help i can't convince her
but i bet her boyfriend can well i'm afraid you're mistaken ma'am i'm not kitagawa's boyfriend
oh what are you we're just in the same class at school and outside of that oh you could say
she gives me money and i do stuff excuse me
today was a major win
all thanks to you you look beautiful up there oh you're too sweet i appreciate it
kitagawa really does seem like a different person i feel a little nervous around her
you got extra dressed up to go out tonight didn't you yeah i'm glad my work paid off i'm so hyped
tonight we're throwing a little birthday party i had to look my best for the occasion
i hope you party the night away i've been looking forward to it for ages now we're actually about to
go pick up the cake i ordered you ready gojo yep i'm ready thanks everybody see you next time
nice to meet you you too and spectacular work today maureen
if they're celebrating a birthday alone he must be her boyfriend i guess he was nervous
hold on maureen's birthday isn't even in this month
huh must be his birthday then
happy birthday to you
it's my angel's birthday happy birthday my precious
thank you so much for being born
you're the best thing that's ever happened to me
thank you for your eternal cuteness my goddess
what madness is this
she's back to her usual self
loving you is the honor just a minute ago she was so
oh
i promise to worship you forever and ever
i got to see a different side of her but at the end of the day
she's still the kitakawa i know
i better slow down i don't want to lose my voice so early
okie dokie time for cake sounds great
now where to put this oh that works well
that works well
cool
okay
so
i
like
Thank you.
New, new, new, new
可愛い界隈
トキメキ感じて
君からの変身まで
可愛い界隈
胸も高鳴る
生まれ変わるよ
君と変わるよ
可愛い界隈
次回予告